selfgrowth.com 2019-06-24

# Online Privacy Policy

This page contains the privacy policy for Self Improvement Online, Inc., SelfGrowth.com and all it's related websites. 

**-What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name,email address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. Like most websites we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information,and track visits to our website. Please refer to the 'do we use cookies?' section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

**\- What do we use your information for?** Any of the information we collect about you may be used in one of the following ways:

* To improve our website  
(We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

* To process transactions  
(We may share or sell information with third parties for marketing or other purposes without your consent)

* To administer acontest, promotion, survey, or other site feature 

*To send periodic emails   
The email address you provide for order processing may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. You may unsubscribe from emails at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link.

**\- How do we protect your information?** We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access the website. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive information is encrypted into our database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.

**-Do we use cookies?** Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookies is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone or by contacting customer service.

**\- Do we disclose any information to outside parties?** We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us inoperating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long asthose parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**\- Third party links** We include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy polices. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**-Online privacy policy only** This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline

**-Terms and Conditions** Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of your website at your site.

**  
-Your Consent** By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy  

**-Changes to our privacy policy** Changes to this privacy policy will be made available on this webpage only.
